{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f1d1cfba6a7876f48bd"},"product_asin":"B07MWBVTLP","QAs":[{"question":"Wether we can add external tap?","answer":"why shoud we add external tap ?It not working as expectedshown all the false reviewsMy money nad time wasted really pathetic experience from pureit and Amazonsee less","votes":"0","username":"Nandu Royal Poola","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Year of the model is 2022 or old one?","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"Nandu Royal Poola","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Low Water pressure is needed or high","answer":"high","votes":"0","username":"Nandu Royal Poola","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"If incase the input water supply stops any chances of purifier getting burn out","answer":"No, machine will stop working because for such conditions these machines have Low Pressure Valve as well as Solenoid Valve.","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Yankee","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will pre filter come with RO unit ?","answer":"Yup, this unit comes with Pre Filter of best quality as compared to the local pre filters.","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Yankee","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Red indicator meaning in product","answer":"Time to replace filters/service.","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Yankee","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Filter price","answer":"Depends on periodic price revisions by the company.","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Yankee","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is first service is free","answer":"Yup, I guess they provide first two services for free.","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Yankee","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the size of sediment filter used  ??","answer":"It is a little bit bigger than the local market variants. But the good thing is its Sediment Filter contains activated Carbon too.","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Yankee","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have connected this to manjeera water which has 200 red but after filter now the tds is 20 .. is it still recommended?","answer":"Yup.","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Yankee","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Having hot and cool water option along copper purification","answer":"No it wont","votes":"0","username":"Raghuveer","date":"2022-04-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f1d1cfba6a7876f48c8"},"product_asin":"B00I8QV2VY","QAs":[{"question":"How many litres of water we get per hour?","answer":"Approx above 50ltr","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Kumar Gupta","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need buttonswitch","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Kumar Gupta","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f1f1cfba6a7876f48cc"},"product_asin":"B08BJN4MP3","QAs":[{"question":"Tds of outlet water?","answer":"40","votes":"0","username":"gaurav","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is tds adjustable? upto what level (number) i can set the tds for output water in this machine? what is the minimum and maximum?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Shiva","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is water discharge rate - for example how much time taken to fill 1 liter bottle from the filter output","answer":"1 minutes","votes":"0","username":"Arindam mondal","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it auto cut and on","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want zero waste water. Ro","answer":"not possible","votes":"0","username":"Arindam mondal","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it capable to purify muddy water","answer":"For that external sediment filter is installed","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is the service backup?","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Arindam mondal","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this product is operate on inverter .","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"They directly connected us for installation or we need to connect them to book an appointment","answer":"They directly contacted me.","votes":"0","username":"Chakradhar Amaravati","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the length of power chord?","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Arindam mondal","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Uv chamber made of?","answer":"The Ultra Violet chamber is lined with Stainless Steel 304 (SS 304) tube which is the highest standard internationally. The UV Cartridge neutralizes and kills any remaining virus or bacteria. All the above filtration elements are of high quality and designed for heavy duty.","votes":"0","username":"Atik","date":"2022-03-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much water purifier  lph?","answer":"Nice","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Kumar","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many years will it take to install it again if we buy u purifier","answer":"Thanks everyone one and Amazon","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Kumar","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it for high iron containing water?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Kumar","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many TDS suitable for model","answer":"Upto 2000 Tds.","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek","date":"2022-03-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it offline?","answer":"No, Electric connection will be required","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek","date":"2022-03-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is the maitenance cost as compared to hul pureit ultima? currently i am having hard time with gkk1 2500, gkk2 2500 and sf filter, service costs.","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Kumar","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manual guide not available with kit","answer":"Kit is not open","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Kumar","date":"2022-03-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"At the time of installation, is there the need of any part for which the payment would be done additionally???","answer":"No such additional part is required. A connection tube may be required to connect the Purifier to water point. That cost between  Rs.25 to 70/-.","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek","date":"2022-03-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f1f1cfba6a7876f48d7"},"product_asin":"B08B27R8MP","QAs":[{"question":"Does the water taste better after purifying?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ViNee ChAudhAry","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Water cooling hota hai","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ViNee ChAudhAry","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"For every 7litres how much water is wasted","answer":"28 l","votes":"0","username":"ViNee ChAudhAry","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the installation person will come to fix it","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ViNee ChAudhAry","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the maintenance cost per year ?","answer":"5k","votes":"0","username":"ViNee ChAudhAry","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f1f1cfba6a7876f48dd"},"product_asin":"B09M45XKKF","QAs":[{"question":"Is pre filter or sediment filter included with this purifier ??","answer":"Yes included but leaking some times","votes":"0","username":"Mohamed Samiulla","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the output for 1 hour","answer":"Ok","votes":"0","username":"Mohamed Samiulla","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Water source at my home is only borewell, Does this water Purifier is enough to purify the water","answer":"Mixed water bore n tap water","votes":"0","username":"Mohamed Samiulla","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is the taste of water?","answer":"Usual taste. The machine doesn’t affect the taste of water","votes":"0","username":"ipsita pradhan","date":"2022-03-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f201cfba6a7876f48e2"},"product_asin":"B094YD54TC","QAs":[{"question":"Is it usefull for alkaline water??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Dr Partha Pratim ghosh","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be the expense every year to change the kit and all?","answer":"Probably the installation guy said Rs. 3000/- will be the annual maintainance,  including filter replacement.","votes":"0","username":"Kashif","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it give a mineral water taste?","answer":"If u have Borewell  water coming in ur tap, it's suitable , it changes it and gives normal tap water taste.","votes":"0","username":"Kashif","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be the expense every year to change the kit and all?","answer":"Probably the installation guy said Rs. 3000/- will be the annual maintainance,  including filter replacement.","votes":"0","username":"Kashif","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it give a mineral water taste?","answer":"If u have Borewell  water coming in ur tap, it's suitable , it changes it and gives normal tap water taste.","votes":"0","username":"Kashif","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f201cfba6a7876f48e5"},"product_asin":"B01N6CA6H6","QAs":[{"question":"Our building has 9 stories and we stay on the 1st floor. Would it work or shall look for some other model ?","answer":"Yes sir this would work.. But at the time of installation technician would check the pressure if its more then you need to install Pressure Reducing Valve to control pressure","votes":"0","username":"Aqua Beat","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What material is the UV chamber made of?","answer":"UV Chamber is made up of ABS Plastic which is food grade plastic","votes":"0","username":"Aqua Beat","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How it retains essential minerals ca and mg?","answer":"It do not remove any minerals as this is UV device so all minerals and salts are retained","votes":"0","username":"Aqua Beat","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are you giving free services as well??","answer":"You can ask free service whenever required within warranty period. Just you need to register on Pureit Helpline...","votes":"0","username":"Aqua Beat","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"why it doesn't have uf filter","answer":"This machine have UV Filtration process it do not have UF Filter","votes":"0","username":"Aqua Beat","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f271cfba6a7876f48f7"},"product_asin":"B0859RHH6X","QAs":[{"question":"How the purifier be installed?","answer":"Worst service by Amazon, they're neither collecting the device now refunding the money.","votes":"0","username":"Preeti Suman","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"how do we get this intalled?  productbdelivered last week mo ome turned up to.instsll","answer":"Worst service by Amazon, I never expected this kind of service, totally useless buying electronic items from Amazon. Very bad experience","votes":"0","username":"Preeti Suman","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"From where can I buy the cover for this product. Its not available on Amazon.","answer":"Buy from authorized distributor, don't buy from Amazon. They're cheating people.","votes":"0","username":"Preeti Suman","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we remove RO filter alone ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Shakti","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used for 2000 tds ?","answer":"No, purchase this product use only single or two person.","votes":"0","username":"Sachin","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can taste be adjusted? If yes how?","answer":"Aquasure Amaze, the RO water filter along with one iron guard changes the taste of water remarkably by reducing the TDS elements.","votes":"0","username":"Pathak","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ro water free installed or charged","answer":"External fillter 800 to 1100","votes":"0","username":"SENAPOTI JOY RAO","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Extra purifier pump","answer":"800 to 1100","votes":"0","username":"SENAPOTI JOY RAO","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cover is available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SENAPOTI JOY RAO","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"I cant seem to fine product manual","answer":"I don’t think there is a manual as such","votes":"0","username":"Ramakrishna","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do this product require additional filter for stop sand etc. With additional cost?","answer":"Entirely depends on your source water quality.For eg I live in mumbai and BMC provided water does not have that many impurities that I need a additional filter.In case you receive impure water at source ie big impurities then having a additional filter is good and the person who comes for installation will have it handy to install at additional cost ( just make sure you cross check and buy at correct price) ask him/ her to call up the service provider and double check the price before payingsee less","votes":"0","username":"pratik","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has TDS adjuster","answer":"It has MTDS. Taste of water is much better","votes":"0","username":"pratik","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the UV chamber made of steel or aluminium?","answer":"Hi, forget about UV. Please do not buy this water filter as this is a worst product to use. In fact, suggest do no use Eureka Forbes even go for any other brand. They're simply thick skinned people & hardly bothered about you as a customer. Here I'm chasing them for the last 5 and a half month almost for a replacement of this junk product but they're so thick skinned, not even bothered. sometimes somebody calls and gives you fake promises about resolving issues but they never do that. Just go for any other brand in the market but not this one. You may use KENT, which we had used for a decade and switched over to Eureka and I still curse that day for my decision.see less","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why service is not good? Why we need to call 5 times every times.","answer":"Service, you must be joking !!!Till now i've written thousands of mail to them, wrote on their homepage in linkedin and all other social platform but sadly they're so thick skinned, nothing matters to them when the product is sold. On my part I've informed all friends, relatives, business relations about bad experiences I'm having with Eureka and not to use their product.see less","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the dimensions?","answer":"Plz do not buy from them until and unless you would like to be another thousands of unfortunate customers who got stuck with this perilous company and it's product.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to replace cartridge? Who and where can we get service n replacement of filters from? As this is exclusive online model ?","answer":"Pathetic product....pathetic company. Yes, exclusive model but total exclusive junk.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"When should we replace the filter and where can I purchase the filter online?","answer":"Actually it depends on the water , how easily dirt accumulates . Taste varies and you can contact nearest eureka executive they will come and check","votes":"0","username":"Manu j.","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it normal for water to keep on filling even if power is not on? My system keeps on filling the tank even if power off as long as water supply is on","answer":"Once the tank is full it should automatically stop.if this is not happening something is wrong.need to call Eureka Forbes customer service to check.","votes":"0","username":"Fahim","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Inside metal or plastic?","answer":"Plastic","votes":"0","username":"mukesh khare","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do they provide free installation","answer":"They do and during installation, these guys recklessly handles the product and breaks it even. I've all experiences and still counting.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is pre filter also part of the pack? Few videos show a white column next to the unit. Is it standalone or are there any additional installation compo?","answer":"No, their installation guys will give you all scary instances and make you buy that separately at a hefty price.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the maintenance cost per year and per month","answer":"Once in a year","votes":"0","username":"mukesh khare","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the filter name for this model? I need to change filter","answer":"never try any product from Eureka Forbes, they're pathetic and so is their products as well. Go for Kent and other brands who at least listens to you.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Iron in water can be removed. ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj K.","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How often should we service the product and how often should we change the filter?","answer":"Membrane service nearly 6000ltr usage, whereas filters specified during service (every 4months )","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-03-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are Installation kit contents?","answer":"two pipes (plastic) for inlet and outlet. One is tap to join to your pipeline valvetype.","votes":"0","username":"mukesh khare","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the machine sets the tds on its own? or the service personnel has to set it?","answer":"Its manual, you can ask service personal to set it as per your requirement.","votes":"0","username":"Chandan M.","date":"2022-03-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use mtds to control tds in aquaguard amaze model?","answer":"Yes. Its a really good technology which can change the water test also.","votes":"0","username":"Prasad m dixit","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"My area pin code 516162 installation available or not?","answer":"Please ask Amazone on this also when you purchase the material it shows you for the services are available or not in your area.","votes":"0","username":"Prasad m dixit","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Our bore water tds level is 800 , can i buy this ro+uv*mtds)","answer":"Donot purchase this machine","votes":"0","username":"AJ","date":"2022-03-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does purifier stop working if filter requires change","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"mukesh khare","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is its filters comes in quaranty","answer":"No warranty on filters is provided","votes":"0","username":"Arup Bose","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much is the maintenance for uv+uf per year? or amc price?","answer":"The installation engineer gave an estimate of around rs 3000 to change the whole set of purification and the change should be done yearly","votes":"0","username":"Arup Bose","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have space constraint in my kitchen cabinet, by seeing the dimensions I feel this product will fit well. But in case it doesn't for, can you please","answer":"H-16.5, w-10.5 D-9.5 dimensions in inch","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj K.","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to raise complaint","answer":"Call Eureka Forbes customer care","votes":"0","username":"Ramakrishna","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we adjust tds manually?","answer":"Yes, but not by ourself, technician will do it.","votes":"0","username":"Ramakrishna","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How it can install","answer":"Don't worry about install, it will be installed by service engineer of company free of cost","votes":"0","username":"Sanjay Garg","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is UF","answer":"Ultra-violet filter","votes":"0","username":"Rajapandian.A","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"When will they come for installation service","answer":"Call the toll free number of Eureka Forbes and the will schedule the installation","votes":"0","username":"Prashant M","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is servicing available for this product?","answer":"You service man not take call and she not come to fit urekagorce ..stiill my hair phone not recived","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Rajput","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Filter municipal water","answer":"Yes it can filter. Just have the water tested for hardness.","votes":"0","username":"Rajapandian.A","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f281cfba6a7876f4902"},"product_asin":"B096NTB9XT","QAs":[{"question":"Can we add Alkaline filter in this?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i get gst invoice","answer":"Aak ur seller","votes":"0","username":"Joy","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the cost of replacement of filters ?","answer":"Iron filter & sediment filter cost 1500 approx. Inside filters including alkaline filter cost around 5200+gst","votes":"0","username":"Joy","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where will we get replacement filter its been only one year and service assistant is asking for more than ₹6000 for replacing filter","answer":"This is pathetic product of eureka Forbes, I have been following up from last one month and there service centre is not replacing the filters. I would suggest you to contact any local repair shop and get it replaced.","votes":"0","username":"Gyan Prakash Rai","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require Running Water?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Joy","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the total filter life?","answer":"Only 4 month and the replacement would cost you more than 10k","votes":"0","username":"Gyan Prakash Rai","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I draw water form stored water without power","answer":"Yes. Water can be drawn without power","votes":"0","username":"MR","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is pre filter with the product or need to purchase","answer":"No, u have to pay extra Rs.1200 for that.","votes":"0","username":"Ejaz Ahmed","date":"2022-03-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it safe to cook rice in this water","answer":"There is no water purified in this machine because the machine doesn't workIt is a useless productDon't waste moneyBuy of a better Company machinr which is working towards customer satisfaction by selling quality productssee less","votes":"0","username":"Rajeev Anand","date":"2022-03-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"plug point connection how match ampare?","answer":"Yes you can","votes":"0","username":"Ranjeev Malik","date":"2022-03-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this ro for borwell water??","answer":"You can but not recommended. If the bore water is too salty, you might have to replace the filter every 2-3 months.","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh Chennamaneni","date":"2022-03-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"It have zinc booster","answer":"Wrost product and service","votes":"0","username":"mukund dadu more","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Should I need to buy extra items (candles,filters, etc) for installation.","answer":"Bad product","votes":"0","username":"mukund dadu more","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How does mtds work? will it mix ro purified water with uf purified water to increase tds??","answer":"Totally wrost product","votes":"0","username":"mukund dadu more","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much copper is in a copper filter?  And how much pure water does the water purifier machine give?  For how long?","answer":"🙏 bad product","votes":"0","username":"mukund dadu more","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have uf ? On the eureka forbes website there's an ivory model has 8 stages purification with uf? Where is the 8 stages prurification model?","answer":"Wrost service product","votes":"0","username":"mukund dadu more","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are the filter cartridges come with electronic chip enabled which enable alarm after filteration of say 6000 litres to change new filter cartridges?","answer":"Yes it will give indication but Chip can get defected and it's not covered under warranty","votes":"0","username":"Rajat","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are the filter cartridges come with electronic chip enabled which enable alarm after filteration of say 6000 litres to change new filter cartridges?","answer":"Yes it will give indication but Chip can get defected and it's not covered under warranty","votes":"0","username":"Rajat","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f291cfba6a7876f490e"},"product_asin":"B07MQ5X54S","QAs":[{"question":"How often do we need to change filters and membranes inside the purifier?","answer":"in worst case, change it within 6 months","votes":"0","username":"JOYJIT MURMU","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"1) Per hour how many liters it filters? 2) does it filter boar water?","answer":"yes it filter boar water","votes":"0","username":"JOYJIT MURMU","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Sound comeing purification  time , it is very  distbance","answer":"if sound coming too much then contact to customer care","votes":"0","username":"JOYJIT MURMU","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"After RO purification water TDS range","answer":"Awesome product..easy to install and easy to use.water quality good.","votes":"0","username":"Najib Ullah Ansary","date":"2022-03-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the maxinum tds after purification","answer":"Good product","votes":"0","username":"Najib Ullah Ansary","date":"2022-03-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"will filters cocer under warranty for first year or not","answer":"nope","votes":"0","username":"JOYJIT MURMU","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do i need to buy pump separately?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Arunprakash","date":"2022-03-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What extra charge is applicable? Its written accessories pump etc extra charge","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Arunprakash","date":"2022-03-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f2d1cfba6a7876f4922"},"product_asin":"B083389Q1B","QAs":[{"question":"What is the usual run time in a 250sq area ?","answer":"Depending on the pollution level of the room.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to search for filter replacement, could not find on amazon ?","answer":"Eureka Forbes customer care can help","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f2e1cfba6a7876f4925"},"product_asin":"B07CWCVFKP","QAs":[{"question":"Guarantee kitni hai","answer":"One year only","votes":"0","username":"samar agencies","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f401cfba6a7876f493f"},"product_asin":"B00UQBIWD0","QAs":[{"question":"Iska filter kaha se milega","answer":"Call toll free number and will get from the service center!","votes":"0","username":"NEW LOTUS ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-03-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f451cfba6a7876f4944"},"product_asin":"B07FZ6Z992","QAs":[{"question":"Can i fit in Supreme extra","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"vk enterprises 1","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this comparable with kent Qnet","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"vk enterprises 1","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this kit compartabile for Kent mineral ro?","answer":"Don't buy it it is duplicate product","votes":"0","username":"Nityagopal De","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why i am refund and my packege return ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Nityagopal De","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this compatible for kent superstar 8ltrs model","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Authorized-Distributor","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i  use it in aquaguard reviva ro?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"A2Z BEST DEAL","date":"2022-03-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this compatible with kent ace plus","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"JAIDEEP ENTERPRISE","date":"2022-03-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this compatible with kent grand 11001","answer":"YES..IT IS COMPATIBLE FOR KENT GRAND. . .","votes":"0","username":"PREET HOME APPLIANCES","date":"2022-03-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f471cfba6a7876f494e"},"product_asin":"B0163X9N32","QAs":[{"question":"Does the fitting ring come with the membrane? cause my membrane broke and it got stuck in fitting ring.","answer":"No sir u get only membrane in pack","votes":"0","username":"Truison Albert","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitable for nasaka  20 ltr water purifier","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-03-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is fit to 10 l kent ro non electric","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Truison Albert","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"It will fit kentgold+ filter","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Truison Albert","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there QR code on product to check genuine product","answer":"Its not genuine my old filter had kent written on membrane side but this has nothing","votes":"0","username":"Truison Albert","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f491cfba6a7876f4954"},"product_asin":"B09P577PXP","QAs":[{"question":"hight kya hai","answer":"4inch","votes":"0","username":"JAI ENTERPRISE261","date":"2022-03-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hight kya hai","answer":"4\" inch","votes":"0","username":"JAI ENTERPRISE261","date":"2022-03-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f4a1cfba6a7876f4957"},"product_asin":"B078B99PFC","QAs":[{"question":"is height 10 inch for the outer dimension (height) of the housing ? and is it supplied with the connectors for pipe on both sides ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"E C enterprises","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this original Eureka Forbes product ? both housing and candle","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Nitin Fadnavis","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we remove the cap of candle?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Nitin Fadnavis","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many candel will I get with this ?","answer":"one","votes":"0","username":"Tinku","date":"2022-03-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it purified  iron.","answer":"It is a pre-filter which removes sediments. You will require a RO filter for removal of iron","votes":"0","username":"Nitin Fadnavis","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f4c1cfba6a7876f495d"},"product_asin":"B09DCPF1HH","QAs":[{"question":"Size of candel","answer":"8inch","votes":"0","username":"WATER LIFE SYSTEMS","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the size of both candles and are both original or duplicate one?","answer":"9'","votes":"0","username":"ss marketing concern","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f4d1cfba6a7876f4962"},"product_asin":"B09JP5F7NR","QAs":[{"question":"Is it single side both outlets","answer":"In out one side","votes":"0","username":"JAI ENTERPRISE261","date":"2022-04-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this a complete sediment filter or filter element only","answer":"Yes it is complete sediment filter","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT SERVICE SOLUTION","date":"2022-03-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f521cfba6a7876f4966"},"product_asin":"B07ZMFMFSQ","QAs":[{"question":"Is it with reverse osmosis technology??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SmartHome Solution","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f541cfba6a7876f4968"},"product_asin":"B07F65HHL9","QAs":[{"question":"Ghar me pani ki tenki hey to pani prsgar se nahi ho to ye mashin laga sakte hey kya","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Viral…","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require water pressure","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"STORE98","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will we get extra candle with this?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Syamal kumar sen","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the flow rate ?","answer":"Two litters par hours","votes":"0","username":"The online seller","date":"2022-03-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f541cfba6a7876f496d"},"product_asin":"B09BKRNLN7","QAs":[{"question":"I can use this with blue star ro+uv","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"JAIDEEP ENTERPRISE","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"For using an inlet valve what size doe this Pre-filter support -1/4\" or 3/8\" Pipe size?","answer":"3/8 pipe size","votes":"0","username":"JAIDEEP ENTERPRISE","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any warranty on this product, cureently used filters broke in 2 -3 weeks.","answer":"No warranty on physical damanges","votes":"0","username":"WATER LIFE SYSTEMS","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compatible with kent max uv water purifier (11013)","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Prem Raj","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contain mounting plate","answer":"Yes, it does","votes":"0","username":"Wasim Ahmed","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"This will remove iron from line water and fit for all type of water filter like Eurekaforbes","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prem Raj","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it included with Installation?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prem Raj","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitable for kent ace copper?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prem Raj","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it on Maxx model??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prem Raj","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitable for kent superb ro, uv, uf, tds control and alkaline water","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"JAIDEEP ENTERPRISE","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use this filter for kent grand plus and kent grand star ro purifiers","answer":"yes this is an external filter which can be used in all types of water purifier so you can easily install it out side of kent grand plus","votes":"0","username":"M/S ASIAN RO","date":"2022-03-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the use of kent pre-filter","answer":"This is a 5 micron filter, it prevents sand soil, due to which the filter inside your kent does not deteriorate quickly","votes":"0","username":"JAIDEEP ENTERPRISE","date":"2022-03-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it with kent water bathroom softner","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"JAIDEEP ENTERPRISE","date":"2022-03-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitable for kent supreme extra(11113)?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"JAIDEEP ENTERPRISE","date":"2022-03-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please tell me candel consumption watter","answer":"5000 litres","votes":"0","username":"M/S ASIAN RO","date":"2022-03-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's suitable for aquaguard royale RO","answer":"It is not useful for Eureka forbes water purfier","votes":"0","username":"WATER LIFE SYSTEMS","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compatible for Kent supreme Plus?","answer":"Yes ! Fully compatible","votes":"0","username":"WATER LIFE SYSTEMS","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compatible for Kent supreme Plus?","answer":"Yes ! Fully compatible","votes":"0","username":"WATER LIFE SYSTEMS","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f541cfba6a7876f4978"},"product_asin":"B07JB26KXR","QAs":[{"question":"Will hot water option available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the latest model in Kent right now?","answer":"Crystal Star, crystal plus","votes":"0","username":"MEGA OFFERR","date":"2022-03-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f551cfba6a7876f497b"},"product_asin":"B07YJKKGBJ","QAs":[{"question":"Is this suitable for aquagurd green RO ?","answer":"No Sir..","votes":"0","username":"Ujju Enterprises","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"This kit is suitable for nano.","answer":"This is only for Reviva and Enhance model, This filter size is big, Not suitable for nano..","votes":"0","username":"Ujju Enterprises","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f5a1cfba6a7876f4986"},"product_asin":"B00V679BEC","QAs":[{"question":"if there is no water in the dispenser , will it affect the heating coil? or does it comes with sensor to detect water before turning coil on?","answer":"I think it will have no effect as when there is no water then the electric connection also should be off .","votes":"0","username":"AKASH G.","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Black  color","answer":"No only on white colour only","votes":"0","username":"samar agencies","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have got this product, but the cooling function is not working. kindly help?","answer":"Did you switch on the button on back side for both cooling and heating (separate buttons), if still you don't see the cooling effect, you may have to contact BlueStar","votes":"0","username":"Potharaju Srinivas","date":"2022-04-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"can you please show the plug picture ? what is plug size ?","answer":"It’s 5 Amps plug three pin only","votes":"0","username":"samar agencies","date":"2022-03-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this work on invertor battery?","answer":"Yes it can, if the power plug has current coming from invertor battery, it takes the same power as it does for any tubelight or fan.","votes":"0","username":"Potharaju Srinivas","date":"2022-03-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much electricity it consume ,is it equal to Fridge or m9re than that","answer":"Same as that of tubelight or fan, definitely not like fridge as the cooling unit it has very small one","votes":"0","username":"Potharaju Srinivas","date":"2022-03-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the cooling chaber has lock?","answer":"no lock","votes":"0","username":"PREMIER REFRIGERATION ENTERPRI…","date":"2022-03-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it an RO","answer":"ITS IS HOT COLD NORMAL WITH REFRIGERATOR ONLY","votes":"0","username":"PREMIER REFRIGERATION ENTERPRI…","date":"2022-03-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f5d1cfba6a7876f4990"},"product_asin":"B07YJMVGF3","QAs":[{"question":"Will sutabil for Dr compact aquaguard, but here dimensions of product 27 x 10x 10 n original dimensions 25.5 x7.6 x 7.6","answer":"I have fitted in compact aqua guard and it fitted properly","votes":"0","username":"Gour","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product dimensions pl here giving packaging dimensions","answer":"The size is 27x10x10 cm. Weight 427 gms.","votes":"0","username":"Gour","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please give actual size of the product, not packaged size.. size..","answer":"It will fit perfectly in compaq model","votes":"0","username":"Mahesh","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f5e1cfba6a7876f4994"},"product_asin":"B08X4TGTTP","QAs":[{"question":"How much water does it waste?","answer":"No waste in uv model","votes":"0","username":"sumati","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f5f1cfba6a7876f4996"},"product_asin":"B07SFZ21BW","QAs":[{"question":"Tds of my society is 900. i wish to get 120-170 tds . can this ro give tds in that range ?","answer":"Hi sir RO meant for TDS reduction by 90%.. In this machine we cannot adjust output TDS but it would give you best reduction basis on water quality","votes":"0","username":"Aqua Beat","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f5f1cfba6a7876f4998"},"product_asin":"B09JLZFHV8","QAs":[{"question":"As this purifier is retaining all the necessary minerals, so is this purifier alkalined also?","answer":"Don't believe, water taste is very bad like tap water. But service is good","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Babu Chepuri","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we have return policy?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Babu Chepuri","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to use during power cut?","answer":"there is a small manual tap with plastic cap at the bottom for use in case of no power or button not functioning","votes":"0","username":"Irfan Ahmad","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is inbuilt tds range of this filter ? can i modify its range based on  water purity of my locality ?","answer":"IT CAN WORK UPTO 2000 PPM","votes":"0","username":"Livpure Smart","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we have TDS adjustment in this ??","answer":"No TDS adjustment .. Inbuilt TDS only ..But that's enough I think soo..","votes":"0","username":"Naresh","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"The storage tank is made of plastic or stainless steel?","answer":"Plastic ..","votes":"0","username":"Naresh","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the tds in water after filteration ?","answer":"200","votes":"0","username":"Naresh","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Subscription plan isn't available in Amazon. Where can we subscribe for plans?","answer":"For this model no subscription based.. Go with their portal you can find it..","votes":"0","username":"Naresh","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"AMC cost?","answer":"please check on amazon.","votes":"0","username":"Livpure Smart","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"AMC cost?","answer":"5500 rupees","votes":"0","username":"Lenin","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it clean copper cartridge automatically?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Zarry Enterprise","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"AMC cost?","answer":"5500 rupees","votes":"0","username":"Lenin","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it clean copper cartridge automatically?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Zarry Enterprise","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"AMC cost?","answer":"5500 rupees","votes":"0","username":"Lenin","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it clean copper cartridge automatically?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Zarry Enterprise","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"AMC cost?","answer":"5500 rupees","votes":"0","username":"Lenin","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f601cfba6a7876f49a1"},"product_asin":"B096NVMQS6","QAs":[{"question":"How many Candels are present inside the Aura ??","answer":"Three. But pls note they are fitted with Microchip. which will mean you would need to change the filter if there's any malfunction.","votes":"0","username":"Amit…","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"1. How long the copper infused water be stored. 2. Does the copper electrodes have auto cleaning, if not how it is cleaned","answer":"Dont buy it its filter is very expensive.","votes":"0","username":"Kunal Tiwari","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"will this remove fluoride ?","answer":"No. It removes onlly suspended particles","votes":"0","username":"katie  sethna","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"can I use 285 tds municipal water?","answer":"No then you should go for an RO","votes":"0","username":"Sunit karmakar","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you have to put water in it by hand?","answer":"Nooooo","votes":"0","username":"Jupyter","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it remove the smell from water if there is any??","answer":"I am not sure but don't use this filter if you water smells. This purifier is meant only for municipal water. Go for RO purifier if your water smells that would be the best choice","votes":"0","username":"Jupyter","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Change  water taste","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SANKET S.","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How often this filters needs to be serviced? Can you mention for many months or a year?","answer":"the company recommends service every 6 months.","votes":"0","username":"Manish Gupta","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about the waste water option,Other purifer have seperate pipe for waste water.","answer":"No need of waste water still you need you take extra filter for outlet of wastage","votes":"0","username":"Suchita Ramteke","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is aura moel without RO technology has wastage of water?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"V.K.","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the water comes out from storage when there is no power?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"avc","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty is from Eureka or Amazon or seller?","answer":"Eureka","votes":"0","username":"SANKET S.","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why the taste is different and same as normal??","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"avc","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outside Filter with box or extra pay for this filter?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ASHOK KUMAR SONGARA","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kindly say the specification of the booster pump?","answer":"I did not install external pump. Pressure is adequate in my society.","votes":"0","username":"SANKET S.","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitable for more than 300 TDS?","answer":"250max to my knowledge","votes":"0","username":"SANKET S.","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to know when is the time to get the filters replaced?","answer":"led light will glowing in differents colour code as per time of change different types of filter.","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ KUMAR","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used for water with TDS 400?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ KUMAR","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it storage water or it works continuslly","answer":"Storage water","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ KUMAR","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"UV chamber made up of which material? Any proof?","answer":"It is made up of fibre","votes":"0","username":"Suchita Ramteke","date":"2022-03-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Free installation gives us","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ KUMAR","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want cover this aqua guard crystal NXT uv+uf cover","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ASHOK KUMAR SONGARA","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Launch date of this product?","answer":"I don't know the launch date of the product. However the product is defective and customer service is very very poor both from Amazon and Eureka Forbes. They don't respond to the requests, when they respond they promise to send the technician for service but hey don't send the technician. I would like to raise a complaint on Amazon and Eureka Forbes as I need to purchase purified drinking water daily in spite of having an Aquaguard purifier at home.see less","votes":"0","username":"Vijay Bhaskara Rao Vasamsetti","date":"2022-03-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"After installation maintainance charges","answer":"You will hv to take Annual Maintainance Contract (AMC) from local Authorised vendor. Pls investigate in your area abt the charges.","votes":"0","username":"V.K.","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this purifier will be suitable for bore or well water","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Export Hut Tosham","date":"2022-03-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is speed of water outlet? Is it fill faster in cup of glass?","answer":"Yes. It is quite good.","votes":"0","username":"Pratss","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it works TDS upto 2500","answer":"No, buy only if TDS is below 600.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f611cfba6a7876f49af"},"product_asin":"B07F6CKMHJ","QAs":[{"question":"Does the product come with external cartridge as shown in the picture?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ravindra Sukthankar","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"In the above product picture, many accessories of complete plumbing kit missing viz. diverter valve, prefilter holder etc.","answer":"All accessories available with products in side box.","votes":"0","username":"Ujju Enterprises","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have an inbuilt pump it","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f631cfba6a7876f49b3"},"product_asin":"B09P52VBJ5","QAs":[{"question":"Is this product suitabe for bluestar aristo ro uv model?","answer":"I don't know. It is OK for Livpure pep model.","votes":"0","username":"Joji Jacob","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f641cfba6a7876f49c0"},"product_asin":"B077VPKJ7Q","QAs":[{"question":"Does it require power to dispense water","answer":"Yes power require","votes":"0","username":"Rudra India Industries","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have active copper feature? (which adds copper ions in the water)","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Ujju Enterprises","date":"2022-04-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be the pressure of out late water to the fridge","answer":"One ltr per minute, it is sufficient and best products for fridge..","votes":"0","username":"Ujju Enterprises","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it delivers stored water in absence of electricity?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Saurabh Kumar","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product stop working or breakdown every 6 months","answer":"My product once in a year.","votes":"0","username":"Saurabh Kumar","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f651cfba6a7876f49c6"},"product_asin":"B00B3VFJY2","QAs":[{"question":"Does it fit to Uniliver pure it excella 9 liter purifier?","answer":"It wont fit","votes":"0","username":"Vinod D","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use this carbon filter in pureit ug+ro classic 5litre?","answer":"No. It is model specific.","votes":"0","username":"Niranjan","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get 14 ltrs capacity  pureit kit","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"RI","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the priceof gkk2 for marvella","answer":"Pl check with the dealer..","votes":"0","username":"RI","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"expiry date ???","answer":"It wont expire","votes":"0","username":"Vinod D","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f651cfba6a7876f49cc"},"product_asin":"B09KNNVPKQ","QAs":[{"question":"It is suitable for livepure pep pro","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ashish Kumar","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How often should we change the filter?","answer":"It should be changed after 5 to 6 month, if water is more dirty then it should be changed after 3 month","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT SERVICE SOLUTION","date":"2022-03-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f651cfba6a7876f49cf"},"product_asin":"B08G5RHSB3","QAs":[{"question":"What is the maintenance of this water purifier","answer":"During wairenty period free service Will be provided. Afterward paid Services.","votes":"0","username":"Dr. A.K.Maity.","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"which brand water filter cover suit for this model","answer":"I don't know. I don't use any cover","votes":"0","username":"Goutam Dey","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is deluxe uv+ Aquaguard eureka forbes provided with candle andcarbon in the new package in the beginning itself.","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Dynamite Dan","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Aaussure is RO or water purifier","answer":"Not RO. UV purifier only.","votes":"0","username":"DD Sathe","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have filter outside of the unit or inside of the unit?","answer":"Inside.","votes":"0","username":"Einstein","date":"2022-03-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation Free & how fast will installation  be done ?","answer":"Very quick and inclusive cost.","votes":"0","username":"DD Sathe","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the service charges","answer":"No charge.","votes":"0","username":"Lilu Besra","date":"2022-03-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does e boiling mean getting hot water?","answer":"No...it means getting water which is equivalent to boiled water...but not hot...","votes":"0","username":"Divya singh","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f661cfba6a7876f49d8"},"product_asin":"B00GX91YA2","QAs":[{"question":"What is the maintenance service cycle? Do we need to replace parts periodically?","answer":"Only you have to maintain the cleaning of the filters every week and replace the same every six months which is provided to you at the time of purchase. Very good and reliable product.","votes":"0","username":"ashok kumar","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f661cfba6a7876f49df"},"product_asin":"B00H3H03Q4","QAs":[{"question":"Will this fit 10 lt purit","answer":"I doubt bcoz it's for 3k liters.","votes":"0","username":"PRAKASH.K.","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is MFD ?","answer":"I Think. It's Manufacturing date.","votes":"0","username":"Kanti","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Advanced germkill kit used at place of classic germkill kit 23 litre","answer":"If the germkill kit fits then I don't see any problem because the filtration would be done. BTW why is it called Advanced Germkill kit? See the bottom line, you should be able to drink quality water from your Purit filter.","votes":"0","username":"Micky D.","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date","answer":"May2021","votes":"0","username":"Vinod","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the date of manafacture?","answer":"Back in 2021","votes":"0","username":"Dharampreet Singh","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this product directly sold by pureit ?","answer":"This  is the same one you get in offline stores","votes":"0","username":"Vani","date":"2022-03-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it fit pureit classic auto fill 18 l?","answer":"It's only 23l","votes":"0","username":"Kanti","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its used in pureit advance max?","answer":"No, it's used in Pureit classic 23 L only","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Nasalapurkar","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f661cfba6a7876f49e7"},"product_asin":"B097TWNFRT","QAs":[{"question":"can you regulate the ph output of water. Need ph value 7.5 ?","answer":"Yes, with help of Iteka Ritz","votes":"0","username":"Yogendra S Shrimali","date":"2022-04-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much water wastage for 1ltr purified water.","answer":"IT WASTES MORE THAN DOUBLE THE TANK CAPACITY","votes":"0","username":"Raj Bhide","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"I received damaged filter, most of the filter received online in this area are damaged as told by technician who came for installation.","answer":"NO SUCH EXPERIENCE.","votes":"0","username":"Raj Bhide","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much water wastage for 1ltr purified water.","answer":"IT WASTES MORE THAN DOUBLE THE TANK CAPACITY","votes":"0","username":"Raj Bhide","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"I received damaged filter, most of the filter received online in this area are damaged as told by technician who came for installation.","answer":"NO SUCH EXPERIENCE.","votes":"0","username":"Raj Bhide","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f661cfba6a7876f49e9"},"product_asin":"B0762HXMTF","QAs":[{"question":"Is it necesaary to remove filterd water from the jug or can keep it in it for along time","answer":"Not value for money, too expensive","votes":"0","username":"Rana Bardhan","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i drink the water instantly after filteration","answer":"Worthless item, too expensive","votes":"0","username":"Rana Bardhan","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you sell the filter for Kent alkaline water filter 3.5 litres model","answer":"Useless item","votes":"0","username":"Rana Bardhan","date":"2022-03-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long we can use? One year or... More how much","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"P. Sukumar","date":"2022-03-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need to buy cartridges, can’t find it in amazon?.","answer":"Not value for money, too expensive","votes":"0","username":"Rana Bardhan","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Question is to manufacturer…some users have said that they are not gettting 9.5 0. can the manufacturer comment on that","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"P. Sukumar","date":"2022-03-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f671cfba6a7876f49f0"},"product_asin":"B00SMFPJG0","QAs":[{"question":"Is it suitable for kent water pitcher","answer":"It is suitable for kent Gold, Gold + and optima water purifiers","votes":"0","username":"KHANDELWAL'S..","date":"2022-03-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f681cfba6a7876f49f2"},"product_asin":"B00H3GWW32","QAs":[{"question":"Whether it can be used for 23 lit classic pure it","answer":"No it can not be.","votes":"0","username":"S.K.Ganguly","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"This kit suitable for pureit minral ro+uv classic modellassic model","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ramesh pednekar","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this 14 l kid to 12l filter for pureit","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ramesh pednekar","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get only candle only,bcs my candle was broken","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"I do not know about capacity  in liters than how can I purchase kit please  suggest me","answer":"Max 2 to 2.5 month. (For 3 people)","votes":"0","username":"Avi","date":"2022-03-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"This kit contains bellow pump or not?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i return Germkit which i brought a few days ago.","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it fit to my pureit eco water saver mineral ro+uv+mf 10l model?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"I ordered 14ltr classic filter kit but this order not delivered till date why ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"I was order this item on 20/11/2021 but till today not deliver. Why??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the seller accept cash on delivery?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it work for 9 liters? if not, than where i can find the battery kit of 9 liters?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rpm05 table top model available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it fits eureka forbes aquasure amrit water purifier??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need polisher rod. is this available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need germ kill kit for puriet ro+uv classic sya62","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"PARTHA SARATHI BHATTACHARYA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need  this product hul pureit germkill kit for classic 14 l","answer":"Yes u can.","votes":"0","username":"S.K.Ganguly","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Sir i need this 2 peices","answer":"It's three pcs.set which needs to change.","votes":"0","username":"S.K.Ganguly","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f681cfba6a7876f49fd"},"product_asin":"B008LN6156","QAs":[{"question":"Will it work for TDS 308?","answer":"No. If TDS more the 300 go with RO.","votes":"0","username":"Vinay Kumar S","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can technician charged for installation for any type of pressure of water","answer":"He did not charge us for the installation.","votes":"0","username":"SAUNI VIDEO PRODUCTIONS","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the storage insulated?","answer":"HiGreetingsNo , insulate.Kent Maxx model is innovative idea for transparent design so water level is visible quickly.In addition to this tank can be removed and clean quickly with unskilled person can do this activity.see less","votes":"0","username":"Leanwork","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it give hot water?","answer":"Hi","votes":"0","username":"Leanwork","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why the water istopped coming and filter became hot?","answer":"Filter becoming hot is natural phenomenon due to pressure and filteration process.","votes":"0","username":"Leanwork","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitable for TDS more than 300?","answer":"No , as per product manual","votes":"0","username":"Zed","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get stainless steel container for water storage instead of harmful plastic tank ?","answer":"It is ABS plastic with food grade quality, Kent Believes  in quality and customers 1st thinking","votes":"0","username":"Leanwork","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Konsa kent h sabse kifayti h","answer":"If your TDS is less than 200 then kent Smart UV is very good.","votes":"0","username":"Leanwork","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f681cfba6a7876f4a06"},"product_asin":"B00E9G8KOY","QAs":[{"question":"Collection Chamber","answer":"?? As such, There is no collection chamber","votes":"0","username":"AMIT","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange order Ko cancel me badalana hai","answer":"Exchange to pureit23ltr classic","votes":"0","username":"SubhashSharma","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"can use pureit 14 ltr classic","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Pranav Sawant","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this be used for purella water purifier","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Abdulrahman","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"have you 'bypassed' the chlorine germkill candle ??   firm assurance pl","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Abdulrahman","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f691cfba6a7876f4a0c"},"product_asin":"B083G2Z15R","QAs":[{"question":"could it be fit for model: ag classic (water filter cum purifier)?","answer":"No This is suitable for us model","votes":"0","username":"CP SRINIVASAN","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f691cfba6a7876f4a0e"},"product_asin":"B09CGQ6FCK","QAs":[{"question":"Is it capable to purify muddy water","answer":"Yes but It will need frequent service to change of parts","votes":"0","username":"Anjli","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange  kent exisiting one","answer":"No . Can check with the technician who visits to install from the company","votes":"0","username":"Anjli","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is prefilter required for water purifier to run ?","answer":"it's depend on your source of water but it's better for your machine to install kent with prefilter","votes":"0","username":"Bhanu Pratap Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who do we have to call for installation or kent will align someone as an auto process","answer":"You don't need to do anything Kent service will call you just after delivery. And install same day","votes":"0","username":"Bhanu Pratap Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"We plan to hang this on the wall; does the appliance body develop cracks over time?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Bhanu Pratap Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whoes install","answer":"Kent service centre sends person to install","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it made in india","answer":"Yes It's totally Made in Bharat","votes":"0","username":"Bhanu Pratap Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the tds adjustment be done by me or only kent mechanic does it?","answer":"It will be great if kent machanic will install, since it is fress of cost so we should call kent for installation and by our self also it can be done,","votes":"0","username":"ayush anand","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many days it will take to supply to the address","answer":"Put ur pin code & Amazon page will have the details","votes":"0","username":"Anjli","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mene 3 month pahle hi khareeda or kharab ho gya or customer service v sahi se nahi mil Rahi 3 din ho gye service Dene nahi a rahe kya karu ?","answer":"Try contacting Amazon to log a complaint with them & at the same time keep calling the company & also write an email for the harassment you are facing.","votes":"0","username":"Anjli","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why dont Amazon remove this low quality wall hanging death from the portal?","answer":"No one is insisting you buy","votes":"0","username":"Anjli","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it not a threat to the life of kids as its falling of the wall with 20 KG weight from 6' hieght?","answer":"The screws are nicely fastened on the wall. So dont worry.","votes":"0","username":"Nitin Vaish","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"After how much time i should change my filter if my water has 300 tds","answer":"Every Quarter","votes":"0","username":"Anjli","date":"2022-03-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Buy back facility","answer":"Only the company can answer","votes":"0","username":"Anjli","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who will install Kent purifier","answer":"The service engineer","votes":"0","username":"Anjli","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"We dont have overhead storage tank, can we connect to municipal supply which somes for 2hours?","answer":"Can do that too. I'll recommend to store water during that time in some clean utensils for use later if the demand is more. RO storage is only 10 litres.","votes":"0","username":"Nitin Vaish","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any possible exchange scheme?","answer":"No aware of... But you may ask the local dealer","votes":"0","username":"Nitin Vaish","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this model be used as a counter top model?","answer":"good to use . good product .","votes":"0","username":"Prithivirajan","date":"2022-03-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's Annual cost after warranty?? I mean filter change and etc","answer":"yes extra cost for filter .","votes":"0","username":"Prithivirajan","date":"2022-03-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much water Wastage per ltr","answer":"U can use the water for watering plants & cleaning  the floor.","votes":"0","username":"Anjli","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6a1cfba6a7876f4a19"},"product_asin":"B09MVPMWCF","QAs":[{"question":"worst  service, they run with no proper technician all are just a labour and dont know how to resolve it.. 15 times i reached and 2 time.","answer":"got installed properly & service is also satisfactory since 3months +","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"does specific plumbing need to be done extra for the installation? What does the accessory kit contain? required taps etc?","answer":"Plumbing required to have inlet at the place of installation","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is the water taste? because our water tds level is 300...","answer":"It’s really very good, taste is good","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-03-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product suitable for 1200 tds","answer":"Yes..as per service engineer.","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj Singh","date":"2022-03-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it add minerals to the water?","answer":"I dont think so. That a diff product","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj Singh","date":"2022-03-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Suitable for borewelk water","answer":"Yes it is suitable for Borewell water, before Filter our Borewell water TDS was 690 and post install and settings of TDS it's now 150","votes":"0","username":"Josh","date":"2022-03-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about installation cost ?","answer":"Zero Installation cost from Trained Representative of Eureka Forbes Aquagaurd","votes":"0","username":"Josh","date":"2022-03-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dimension","answer":"About 1 ft width, 1.5 ft height and 10inches depth. Adaptor unit is and one filter is outside","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj Singh","date":"2022-03-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this come with pre filter? The reason I am asking is that the delivey guy insisted for installation and its costed additional Rs 1200.","answer":"It can with Pre Filter in Box no additional charge billed","votes":"0","username":"Josh","date":"2022-03-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the tds value of water output. As ours is at 005. Is water good for drinking.","answer":"Our Tds is 250 and not getting a proper response from eureka forbes to get it fixed as well, wasted money on wrong product","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6a1cfba6a7876f4a24"},"product_asin":"B07WYX6P2V","QAs":[{"question":"Can I unbox this after delivery ?","answer":"yes you can","votes":"0","username":"Amit kumar","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it give cold and hot water, both?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"karthikeyan pattem","date":"2022-03-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Have mineraliser ?","answer":"Yes.But only in Bluestar opulus alkaline model","votes":"0","username":"Likhith Gopisetty","date":"2022-03-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the company provide us service to clean the purifier?","answer":"Yes! you can raise request on provided customer care number.","votes":"0","username":"Abhijit Patil","date":"2022-03-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6b1cfba6a7876f4a29"},"product_asin":"B08CSG8TC3","QAs":[{"question":"can we connect the aquaguard with wifi","answer":"No you cannot.","votes":"0","username":"Pratik Bhatt","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 4years free service??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Tarok Nath Sarkar","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Contact no to manufacture","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Tarok Nath Sarkar","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How fast can it dispense water?","answer":"It works fine if filled properly. However, Even in Mumbai they try & push for a 3500+ rs water pump. Its just a way for the third part installers to up-sell.","votes":"0","username":"Pratik Bhatt","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation included","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Tarok Nath Sarkar","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6c1cfba6a7876f4a36"},"product_asin":"B0958Q3K68","QAs":[{"question":"For using an inlet valve what size doe this Purifier support -1/4\" or 3/8\" Pipe size?","answer":"You can use adopters and use it in any pipe line. But the waste water thrown out is very high and hence for houses with limited water supply, this water filter is a waste.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"In this product(Kent Elegant Lite), what is the amount of waste water coming out?","answer":"Yes. Water wastage is very high in this KENT. It is better to go in for just water filter instead of RO, if you are using Corporation water.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What does the tds controller do? what is the max and min tds it will allow? can it be manually controlled?","answer":"I dont think tds is user controllable. If you are using Corporation water, it is better to go in for just filter instead of RO. There is lot of water wastage in RO.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Maintenance cost","answer":"Zero since purchased.","votes":"0","username":"yogesh chandra srivastav","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi, I have ordered last week monday and its delivered by 2 nd june Thursday, may i know when the installation will come and complete? Please check","answer":"My purifier was installed within 3 days of delivery.","votes":"0","username":"yogesh chandra srivastav","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about the installation?","answer":"All cost included in order.","votes":"0","username":"yogesh chandra srivastav","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Maintenance cost","answer":"Regular maintenance is must. Lot of wastage of water is there for RO reject. If you have limited water, then this is a waste.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi, I have ordered last week monday and its delivered by 2 nd june Thursday, may i know when the installation will come and complete? Please check","answer":"My purifier was installed within 3 days of delivery.","votes":"0","username":"yogesh chandra srivastav","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about the installation?","answer":"All cost included in order.","votes":"0","username":"yogesh chandra srivastav","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Maintenance cost","answer":"Regular maintenance is must. Lot of wastage of water is there for RO reject. If you have limited water, then this is a waste.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Maintenance cost","answer":"Regular maintenance is must. Lot of wastage of water is there for RO reject. If you have limited water, then this is a waste.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6d1cfba6a7876f4a3a"},"product_asin":"B09JM2SGSX","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have an outlet pipe to release waste water ?How much waste water is released per litre ?","answer":"Yes ! it have outlet pipe for waste water.","votes":"0","username":"Livpure Smart","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pre filter is fitted inside or outside?","answer":"Livpure RO is very good but but installation and service engineer have not any knowledge....","votes":"0","username":"Manish Prajapati","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it safe to drink artificially added minerals (mineralizer) water,as company is claiming we can get tds to a certain level by using mineralizer.","answer":"RO IS BEST BUT SERVICE ENGINEER HAVE NO ANY KNOWLEDGE...","votes":"0","username":"Manish Prajapati","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the highest tds adjustment in it","answer":"2000","votes":"0","username":"Pranay Pasricha","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it smart ro. Can be monitored on mobile","answer":"No app connectivity. Not a smart RO","votes":"0","username":"Venkat","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"My water tds is 500 to 650. would it work. and how much it will reduce tds.","answer":"It should reduce TDS significantly as I am living in NCR will very high TDS.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it useful for bore water?","answer":"IT CAN WORK UPTO 2000 PPM","votes":"0","username":"Livpure Smart","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it useful for bore water?","answer":"IT CAN WORK UPTO 2000 PPM","votes":"0","username":"Livpure Smart","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we adjust TDS manually by our choice?","answer":"Taste enhancer is fitted in the machine ,need to open for adjust","votes":"0","username":"Livpure Smart","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How about cleaning?","answer":"Taste enhancer is fitted in the machine ,need to open for adjust","votes":"0","username":"Livpure Smart","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it support livpure mobile app","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"Livpure Smart","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the storage tank made of stainless steel?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"kiran reddy","date":"2022-03-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this filter has its own motor? To fetch water in low water pressure areas?","answer":"Yes, it has its own motor.","votes":"0","username":"kiran reddy","date":"2022-03-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the installation cost..??","answer":"Free","votes":"0","username":"Upendra kR Rai","date":"2022-03-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the water wastage in this purifier? Also, how much does replacement filters cost?","answer":"Water wastage is very low around 20%.","votes":"0","username":"kiran reddy","date":"2022-03-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6d1cfba6a7876f4a45"},"product_asin":"B008QE1OIO","QAs":[{"question":"Please give the details of catridges. What does the catridge contain? Does it contain chalk or something like old steel water filters.","answer":"Pls pls don't buy this product. Catridge would not work more than 20-25 days its kind of bulk paper. Total waste of money . No customer care can take complaint/nobody visit to repair this product from Eureka.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use this to filter river water with soil contents","answer":"Yeah a little bit","votes":"0","username":"Thomson","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use this to filter river water with soil contents","answer":"Yeah a little bit","votes":"0","username":"Thomson","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ish ka filter kaha meliga","answer":"Refill filter cartridges ke liye Model Number batake toll free helpline 1860 266 1177 par phon kijiye.","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model is this?","answer":"Eureka Forbes AquaSure Amrit 20L","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do price deta hai 2499 aur 3999 ek hi product ka","answer":"Only single unit","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ish ka filter kaha meliga","answer":"Refill filter cartridges ke liye Model Number batake toll free helpline 1860 266 1177 par phon kijiye.","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model is this?","answer":"Eureka Forbes AquaSure Amrit 20L","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do price deta hai 2499 aur 3999 ek hi product ka","answer":"Only single unit","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ish ka filter kaha meliga","answer":"Refill filter cartridges ke liye Model Number batake toll free helpline 1860 266 1177 par phon kijiye.","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model is this?","answer":"Eureka Forbes AquaSure Amrit 20L","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do price deta hai 2499 aur 3999 ek hi product ka","answer":"Only single unit","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ish ka filter kaha meliga","answer":"Refill filter cartridges ke liye Model Number batake toll free helpline 1860 266 1177 par phon kijiye.","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model is this?","answer":"Eureka Forbes AquaSure Amrit 20L","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do price deta hai 2499 aur 3999 ek hi product ka","answer":"Only single unit","votes":"0","username":"Tonol Murmu","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6e1cfba6a7876f4a47"},"product_asin":"B09BL2KHQW","QAs":[{"question":"Kitne micro. Tak ko filter ker skti hai...???","answer":"1-micron","votes":"0","username":"M/S ASIAN RO","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this fit kent excell plus","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"mrinal","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it original kent product or a duplicate one? i purchased from online website and a kent service engineer told me that it was a fake.","answer":"Yes this is orignal kent product","votes":"0","username":"WATER LIFE SYSTEMS","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it refundable?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Shreeram Iyer","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6e1cfba6a7876f4a49"},"product_asin":"B08J8H8G74","QAs":[{"question":"For how much TDS range this will be suitable?","answer":"Average","votes":"0","username":"SUNIL KUMAR PADHI","date":"2022-03-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it purify well water","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"P.Raghuramreddy","date":"2022-03-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Well water","answer":"Yes it will purifier well water also","votes":"0","username":"P.Raghuramreddy","date":"2022-03-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please specify the power consumption","answer":"40w bulb","votes":"0","username":"P.Raghuramreddy","date":"2022-03-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much is the AMC for this?","answer":"Annual maintenance cost is depend on in put water, 300 for 2 months hardly","votes":"0","username":"P.Raghuramreddy","date":"2022-03-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is good for borwel water","answer":"Yes it is","votes":"0","username":"P.Raghuramreddy","date":"2022-03-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it fit for TDS 1400?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"P.Raghuramreddy","date":"2022-03-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6e1cfba6a7876f4a52"},"product_asin":"B01HXUJB2W","QAs":[{"question":"date of manufacturing of this product","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"MAA.ENTERPRISES.","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much candle in this filter","answer":"Sediment, UV lamp, UF Hollow Membrane, Carbon Block. 4 candles.","votes":"0","username":"King","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Our borewell water tds is 350.  is this product is ok ?","answer":"As per WHO standards yes.","votes":"0","username":"King","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6f1cfba6a7876f4a57"},"product_asin":"B009DA69KS","QAs":[{"question":"It has float?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Star","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"I was sent used dirty product. It still had water in it.You should check before sending items","answer":"I received brand new","votes":"0","username":"Star","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much time it takes to filter.?  When i used for the first time, it took me 5 minutes to filter... Is there anything wrong with the filterarion pro","answer":"Usually it takes that much time","votes":"0","username":"Star","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f6f1cfba6a7876f4a5b"},"product_asin":"B009DA69W6","QAs":[{"question":"Is it able to change the taste of salty water ?","answer":"No.not change the water taste","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"If my inlet water TDS is 450 is this product suitable?","answer":"Not at all it's just drain your water from upper container to lower container. Please consume safe filtered water buy purifier of your budget, don't compromise with health.","votes":"0","username":"Mrudula","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it convert hard water to soft water?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"pankaj b.","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"If tds is 400, what will be the tds after filter?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mrudula","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it good for lucknow municipality water which contain alot of chlorine i need to.wash hairs with this","answer":"If membrane problem water not flo","votes":"0","username":"S,.Tirupathi Rao","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या यह पानी का पीला पन दूर कर सकता हैं","answer":"Any filter not change colour of water","votes":"0","username":"Vinod yarav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tds is 70 my home can use this water purified","answer":"yes as per company recommendation. you can easily used this product at low tds water.","votes":"0","username":"DEALS ADDA","date":"2022-03-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used to purify ground water?","answer":"No…it’s not RO. Only municipal water of certain TDS.","votes":"0","username":"Bhujanga Sayana","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used to purify ground water?","answer":"Yes, it can be.","votes":"0","username":"Tapas Paul","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used to purify ground water?","answer":"Yes, it can be.","votes":"0","username":"Tapas Paul","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used to purify ground water?","answer":"Yes, it can be.","votes":"0","username":"Tapas Paul","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f701cfba6a7876f4a63"},"product_asin":"B08BPLRWNS","QAs":[{"question":"If i buy now, How long the free service will be covered and can you please share the detail terms and conditions of the warranty?","answer":"Warranty is for one year. So, you will get free service for one year. If you download their mobile application and send service requests using that application, you will get the free service extended for three more years. That means, free service for a total of four years, provided that you register your requests via the mobile application.see less","votes":"0","username":"Dheeraj Sharma","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the material of UV chamber made of???stainless steel or aluminum?","answer":"Plastic","votes":"0","username":"Alpesh parmar","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What if the tds is already at 70-80 due to corporation water supply. will it ensure that required minerals are added","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Aditi Mittal","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"how much tds in raw water can the membranes easily filter?","answer":"Right now..In my home we are using regular water with 242 TDS and filtered by kent it is showing 74 TDS.","votes":"0","username":"Akbar Mulani","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is tds adjustable? upto what level (number) i can set the tds for output water in this machine? what is the minimum and maximum?","answer":"No it's set automated by the company","votes":"0","username":"Alpesh parmar","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we choose the installation date after one or two weeks of delivery ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Alpesh parmar","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many days it will take for installation?","answer":"1-2 days","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much water will wastage?","answer":"Forget about the water wastage, the after sales service is terrible and you will regret as I am regretting now.","votes":"0","username":"Rosemary Gomes","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What support I will get on warranty extension?","answer":"As after sales service is terrible so expect to get some terrible support only.","votes":"0","username":"Rosemary Gomes","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"RO thanda garam","answer":"Nice","votes":"0","username":"Praveen","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use this alkaline purifier for our borewell water?? Is it suitable?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this be exchanged for aquasure Nano RO","answer":"Exchange available on flipkart","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Water tank capacity","answer":"8 ltr","votes":"0","username":"Amal","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it work for 1300 tds water","answer":"Don't buys this one.. this is. Not met as expected.. buys something else .","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-03-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"How the waste water goes to overhead tank","answer":"It doesn't go.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-03-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i don't want to re-circulates the wastage water to my overhead tank, can i let it go to drainage pipe? because i have seen mixed reviews.","answer":"Kent kabhi mat lena . Eski service very poor hai","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-03-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please suggest best kent model for a 3 members family. Our tds is 260","answer":"Dont buy any purifier with RO in it as it will destroy your TDS level. Anyways dont buy kent the after sales service is terrible.","votes":"0","username":"Rosemary Gomes","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require voltage stabiliser","answer":"Not required","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f711cfba6a7876f4a73"},"product_asin":"B0095S9JU0","QAs":[{"question":"What is the maintenance of this water purifier","answer":"During wairenty period free service Will be provided. Afterward paid Services.","votes":"0","username":"Dr. A.K.Maity.","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"which brand water filter cover suit for this model","answer":"I don't know. I don't use any cover","votes":"0","username":"Goutam Dey","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is deluxe uv+ Aquaguard eureka forbes provided with candle andcarbon in the new package in the beginning itself.","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Dynamite Dan","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Aaussure is RO or water purifier","answer":"Not RO. UV purifier only.","votes":"0","username":"DD Sathe","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have filter outside of the unit or inside of the unit?","answer":"Inside.","votes":"0","username":"Einstein","date":"2022-03-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation Free & how fast will installation  be done ?","answer":"Very quick and inclusive cost.","votes":"0","username":"DD Sathe","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the service charges","answer":"No charge.","votes":"0","username":"Lilu Besra","date":"2022-03-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does e boiling mean getting hot water?","answer":"No...it means getting water which is equivalent to boiled water...but not hot...","votes":"0","username":"Divya singh","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f721cfba6a7876f4a85"},"product_asin":"B0085KK9OY","QAs":[{"question":"Water purifier","answer":"Don't buy it","votes":"0","username":"Suraj p.","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where i can buy the spare parts? while changing the uf filter, the nut got broken.","answer":"Available on Amazon","votes":"0","username":"MOHAN","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f721cfba6a7876f4a88"},"product_asin":"B0095PD2OC","QAs":[{"question":"What is the maintenance of this water purifier","answer":"During wairenty period free service Will be provided. Afterward paid Services.","votes":"0","username":"Dr. A.K.Maity.","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"which brand water filter cover suit for this model","answer":"I don't know. I don't use any cover","votes":"0","username":"Goutam Dey","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is deluxe uv+ Aquaguard eureka forbes provided with candle andcarbon in the new package in the beginning itself.","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Dynamite Dan","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Aaussure is RO or water purifier","answer":"Not RO. UV purifier only.","votes":"0","username":"DD Sathe","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have filter outside of the unit or inside of the unit?","answer":"Inside.","votes":"0","username":"Einstein","date":"2022-03-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation Free & how fast will installation  be done ?","answer":"Very quick and inclusive cost.","votes":"0","username":"DD Sathe","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the service charges","answer":"No charge.","votes":"0","username":"Lilu Besra","date":"2022-03-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does e boiling mean getting hot water?","answer":"No...it means getting water which is equivalent to boiled water...but not hot...","votes":"0","username":"Divya singh","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f721cfba6a7876f4a91"},"product_asin":"B07SQX4GHH","QAs":[{"question":"Can we adjust tds of our choice","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Avishek Mondal","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many Post installation service, if any, are there?","answer":"2","votes":"0","username":"Sanjoy Mukherjee…","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it electric or non electric","answer":"It’s electric operated","votes":"0","username":"LK Arora","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any free servicing available after installation","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"CHITIJ MAYANK","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"After receiving machine installation there's is problem leakage at top Cove due to Machine istal by by raw hand mechnic not your service engineer pune","answer":"Completed.","votes":"0","username":"Rajkumar Mukherjee","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"After receiving machine installation there's is problem leakage at top Cove due to Machine istal by by raw hand mechnic not your service engineer pune","answer":"Check the horizontal level if okayThen the float switch may not be working properly.Better escalate with Eureka Forbes on their websitesee less","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-03-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"After receiving machine installation there's is problem leakage at top Cove due to Machine istal by by raw hand mechnic not your service engineer pune","answer":"Contact the supplier or Eureka Forb directly","votes":"0","username":"LK Arora","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get this purifier delivered at a place but get it installed at different place?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Rajkumar Mukherjee","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it have mineral guard technology as well that retains natural minerals that are part of input water?","answer":"yes that is..but not properly working.","votes":"0","username":"BRIJESH SINGH","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we have to fill this purifier manually or it does it automatically?","answer":"Automatically.","votes":"0","username":"MD SAHBAZ","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to clean the water tank","answer":"People will come from the company, we can't do cleaning as it's difficult to open the box and find out how to clean it","votes":"0","username":"vishal jagani","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is cost of replacing the filter part after 1 yr?","answer":"Bro, it will have to be changed only after every three months.charge 4500rs","votes":"0","username":"BRIJESH SINGH","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Green light is not there anymore. Earlier it was on.","answer":"Check water source. If it's fine, raise a complaint. Probably PCB board needs to be replaced","votes":"0","username":"Arun","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"The body of my Aquasure is broken. Upon complaint it was not changed. Where to get a new body and how much will it cost?","answer":"Is it's under warranty then they have to change if not then also the must have those parts easily available, only thing they will extra charges","votes":"0","username":"vishal jagani","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f721cfba6a7876f4aa0"},"product_asin":"B08FYVXWYB","QAs":[{"question":"What is the maintenance of this water purifier","answer":"During wairenty period free service Will be provided. Afterward paid Services.","votes":"0","username":"Dr. A.K.Maity.","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"which brand water filter cover suit for this model","answer":"I don't know. I don't use any cover","votes":"0","username":"Goutam Dey","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is deluxe uv+ Aquaguard eureka forbes provided with candle andcarbon in the new package in the beginning itself.","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Dynamite Dan","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Aaussure is RO or water purifier","answer":"Not RO. UV purifier only.","votes":"0","username":"DD Sathe","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have filter outside of the unit or inside of the unit?","answer":"Inside.","votes":"0","username":"Einstein","date":"2022-03-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation Free & how fast will installation  be done ?","answer":"Very quick and inclusive cost.","votes":"0","username":"DD Sathe","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the service charges","answer":"No charge.","votes":"0","username":"Lilu Besra","date":"2022-03-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does e boiling mean getting hot water?","answer":"No...it means getting water which is equivalent to boiled water...but not hot...","votes":"0","username":"Divya singh","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f731cfba6a7876f4aa9"},"product_asin":"B0073QKROI","QAs":[{"question":"Can this be directly connected to the water dispenser in my Samasung side by side refrigerator?","answer":"Yes you need to install Sterling RO for connecting to Samsung fridge.","votes":"0","username":"Leanwork","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f731cfba6a7876f4aab"},"product_asin":"B07YC8JHMB","QAs":[{"question":"How the purifier be installed?","answer":"Worst service by Amazon, they're neither collecting the device now refunding the money.","votes":"0","username":"Preeti Suman","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"how do we get this intalled?  productbdelivered last week mo ome turned up to.instsll","answer":"Worst service by Amazon, I never expected this kind of service, totally useless buying electronic items from Amazon. Very bad experience","votes":"0","username":"Preeti Suman","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"From where can I buy the cover for this product. Its not available on Amazon.","answer":"Buy from authorized distributor, don't buy from Amazon. They're cheating people.","votes":"0","username":"Preeti Suman","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we remove RO filter alone ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Shakti","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used for 2000 tds ?","answer":"No, purchase this product use only single or two person.","votes":"0","username":"Sachin","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can taste be adjusted? If yes how?","answer":"Aquasure Amaze, the RO water filter along with one iron guard changes the taste of water remarkably by reducing the TDS elements.","votes":"0","username":"Pathak","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ro water free installed or charged","answer":"External fillter 800 to 1100","votes":"0","username":"SENAPOTI JOY RAO","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Extra purifier pump","answer":"800 to 1100","votes":"0","username":"SENAPOTI JOY RAO","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cover is available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SENAPOTI JOY RAO","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"I cant seem to fine product manual","answer":"I don’t think there is a manual as such","votes":"0","username":"Ramakrishna","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do this product require additional filter for stop sand etc. With additional cost?","answer":"Entirely depends on your source water quality.For eg I live in mumbai and BMC provided water does not have that many impurities that I need a additional filter.In case you receive impure water at source ie big impurities then having a additional filter is good and the person who comes for installation will have it handy to install at additional cost ( just make sure you cross check and buy at correct price) ask him/ her to call up the service provider and double check the price before payingsee less","votes":"0","username":"pratik","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has TDS adjuster","answer":"It has MTDS. Taste of water is much better","votes":"0","username":"pratik","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the UV chamber made of steel or aluminium?","answer":"Hi, forget about UV. Please do not buy this water filter as this is a worst product to use. In fact, suggest do no use Eureka Forbes even go for any other brand. They're simply thick skinned people & hardly bothered about you as a customer. Here I'm chasing them for the last 5 and a half month almost for a replacement of this junk product but they're so thick skinned, not even bothered. sometimes somebody calls and gives you fake promises about resolving issues but they never do that. Just go for any other brand in the market but not this one. You may use KENT, which we had used for a decade and switched over to Eureka and I still curse that day for my decision.see less","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why service is not good? Why we need to call 5 times every times.","answer":"Service, you must be joking !!!Till now i've written thousands of mail to them, wrote on their homepage in linkedin and all other social platform but sadly they're so thick skinned, nothing matters to them when the product is sold. On my part I've informed all friends, relatives, business relations about bad experiences I'm having with Eureka and not to use their product.see less","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the dimensions?","answer":"Plz do not buy from them until and unless you would like to be another thousands of unfortunate customers who got stuck with this perilous company and it's product.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to replace cartridge? Who and where can we get service n replacement of filters from? As this is exclusive online model ?","answer":"Pathetic product....pathetic company. Yes, exclusive model but total exclusive junk.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"When should we replace the filter and where can I purchase the filter online?","answer":"Actually it depends on the water , how easily dirt accumulates . Taste varies and you can contact nearest eureka executive they will come and check","votes":"0","username":"Manu j.","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it normal for water to keep on filling even if power is not on? My system keeps on filling the tank even if power off as long as water supply is on","answer":"Once the tank is full it should automatically stop.if this is not happening something is wrong.need to call Eureka Forbes customer service to check.","votes":"0","username":"Fahim","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Inside metal or plastic?","answer":"Plastic","votes":"0","username":"mukesh khare","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do they provide free installation","answer":"They do and during installation, these guys recklessly handles the product and breaks it even. I've all experiences and still counting.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is pre filter also part of the pack? Few videos show a white column next to the unit. Is it standalone or are there any additional installation compo?","answer":"No, their installation guys will give you all scary instances and make you buy that separately at a hefty price.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the maintenance cost per year and per month","answer":"Once in a year","votes":"0","username":"mukesh khare","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the filter name for this model? I need to change filter","answer":"never try any product from Eureka Forbes, they're pathetic and so is their products as well. Go for Kent and other brands who at least listens to you.","votes":"0","username":"Soumitra Ghosh","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Iron in water can be removed. ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj K.","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How often should we service the product and how often should we change the filter?","answer":"Membrane service nearly 6000ltr usage, whereas filters specified during service (every 4months )","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-03-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are Installation kit contents?","answer":"two pipes (plastic) for inlet and outlet. One is tap to join to your pipeline valvetype.","votes":"0","username":"mukesh khare","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the machine sets the tds on its own? or the service personnel has to set it?","answer":"Its manual, you can ask service personal to set it as per your requirement.","votes":"0","username":"Chandan M.","date":"2022-03-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use mtds to control tds in aquaguard amaze model?","answer":"Yes. Its a really good technology which can change the water test also.","votes":"0","username":"Prasad m dixit","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"My area pin code 516162 installation available or not?","answer":"Please ask Amazone on this also when you purchase the material it shows you for the services are available or not in your area.","votes":"0","username":"Prasad m dixit","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Our bore water tds level is 800 , can i buy this ro+uv*mtds)","answer":"Donot purchase this machine","votes":"0","username":"AJ","date":"2022-03-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does purifier stop working if filter requires change","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"mukesh khare","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is its filters comes in quaranty","answer":"No warranty on filters is provided","votes":"0","username":"Arup Bose","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much is the maintenance for uv+uf per year? or amc price?","answer":"The installation engineer gave an estimate of around rs 3000 to change the whole set of purification and the change should be done yearly","votes":"0","username":"Arup Bose","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have space constraint in my kitchen cabinet, by seeing the dimensions I feel this product will fit well. But in case it doesn't for, can you please","answer":"H-16.5, w-10.5 D-9.5 dimensions in inch","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj K.","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to raise complaint","answer":"Call Eureka Forbes customer care","votes":"0","username":"Ramakrishna","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we adjust tds manually?","answer":"Yes, but not by ourself, technician will do it.","votes":"0","username":"Ramakrishna","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How it can install","answer":"Don't worry about install, it will be installed by service engineer of company free of cost","votes":"0","username":"Sanjay Garg","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is UF","answer":"Ultra-violet filter","votes":"0","username":"Rajapandian.A","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"When will they come for installation service","answer":"Call the toll free number of Eureka Forbes and the will schedule the installation","votes":"0","username":"Prashant M","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is servicing available for this product?","answer":"You service man not take call and she not come to fit urekagorce ..stiill my hair phone not recived","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Rajput","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Filter municipal water","answer":"Yes it can filter. Just have the water tested for hardness.","votes":"0","username":"Rajapandian.A","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f731cfba6a7876f4ab6"},"product_asin":"B08KHPDG3N","QAs":[{"question":"How many Candels are present inside the Aura ??","answer":"Three. But pls note they are fitted with Microchip. which will mean you would need to change the filter if there's any malfunction.","votes":"0","username":"Amit…","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"1. How long the copper infused water be stored. 2. Does the copper electrodes have auto cleaning, if not how it is cleaned","answer":"Dont buy it its filter is very expensive.","votes":"0","username":"Kunal Tiwari","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"will this remove fluoride ?","answer":"No. It removes onlly suspended particles","votes":"0","username":"katie  sethna","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"can I use 285 tds municipal water?","answer":"No then you should go for an RO","votes":"0","username":"Sunit karmakar","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you have to put water in it by hand?","answer":"Nooooo","votes":"0","username":"Jupyter","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it remove the smell from water if there is any??","answer":"I am not sure but don't use this filter if you water smells. This purifier is meant only for municipal water. Go for RO purifier if your water smells that would be the best choice","votes":"0","username":"Jupyter","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Change  water taste","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SANKET S.","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How often this filters needs to be serviced? Can you mention for many months or a year?","answer":"the company recommends service every 6 months.","votes":"0","username":"Manish Gupta","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about the waste water option,Other purifer have seperate pipe for waste water.","answer":"No need of waste water still you need you take extra filter for outlet of wastage","votes":"0","username":"Suchita Ramteke","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is aura moel without RO technology has wastage of water?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"V.K.","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the water comes out from storage when there is no power?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"avc","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty is from Eureka or Amazon or seller?","answer":"Eureka","votes":"0","username":"SANKET S.","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why the taste is different and same as normal??","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"avc","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outside Filter with box or extra pay for this filter?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ASHOK KUMAR SONGARA","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kindly say the specification of the booster pump?","answer":"I did not install external pump. Pressure is adequate in my society.","votes":"0","username":"SANKET S.","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitable for more than 300 TDS?","answer":"250max to my knowledge","votes":"0","username":"SANKET S.","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to know when is the time to get the filters replaced?","answer":"led light will glowing in differents colour code as per time of change different types of filter.","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ KUMAR","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used for water with TDS 400?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ KUMAR","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it storage water or it works continuslly","answer":"Storage water","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ KUMAR","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"UV chamber made up of which material? Any proof?","answer":"It is made up of fibre","votes":"0","username":"Suchita Ramteke","date":"2022-03-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Free installation gives us","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ KUMAR","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want cover this aqua guard crystal NXT uv+uf cover","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ASHOK KUMAR SONGARA","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Launch date of this product?","answer":"I don't know the launch date of the product. However the product is defective and customer service is very very poor both from Amazon and Eureka Forbes. They don't respond to the requests, when they respond they promise to send the technician for service but hey don't send the technician. I would like to raise a complaint on Amazon and Eureka Forbes as I need to purchase purified drinking water daily in spite of having an Aquaguard purifier at home.see less","votes":"0","username":"Vijay Bhaskara Rao Vasamsetti","date":"2022-03-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"After installation maintainance charges","answer":"You will hv to take Annual Maintainance Contract (AMC) from local Authorised vendor. Pls investigate in your area abt the charges.","votes":"0","username":"V.K.","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this purifier will be suitable for bore or well water","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Export Hut Tosham","date":"2022-03-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is speed of water outlet? Is it fill faster in cup of glass?","answer":"Yes. It is quite good.","votes":"0","username":"Pratss","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it works TDS upto 2500","answer":"No, buy only if TDS is below 600.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62a18f741cfba6a7876f4ac1"},"product_asin":"B08HWXFRKK","QAs":[{"question":"What will be the tds value after filtration?","answer":"Best purified","votes":"0","username":"GHULAM SABIR SHAMSI","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the yearly maintainence charge","answer":"2 to 3 thousand approx","votes":"0","username":"Vinod Dhatterwal…","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the R.O number","answer":"R.O number is which is mentioned on R.O filter inside the purifier","votes":"0","username":"Srinivas","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we have to install a sediment filter, is it compulsory ?","answer":"It is not mandatory to install external sediment filter since purifier already having inbuilt sediment filter, if your water is hard or dusty then it is suggested to use","votes":"0","username":"Srinivas","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it works in high tds water","answer":"Not sure what would be the high tds , but I’m using this purifier for tds of 1500 which was shown for my bore water and after purifying it is showing 120 , as per my knowledge it will purify max 90 of ur pre-filter water tds","votes":"0","username":"Srinivas","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I already have the screws mounted for wall mount. How to check if this will fix in the same?","answer":"If you already screws mounted to wall then you have to measure the new purifier length and high is same Or not other wise you to alter accordingly, any way installation technician will care of it. You don’t need worry about it","votes":"1","username":"Srinivas","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work well on salty or hard water??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vaibhav","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who will install the RO in my house","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vaibhav","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"If the filter is reusable... it ll be a good product... Bcoz each year we can't pay for 5000 for filter alone","answer":"For any RO purifier filer needs to be replaced every 1 to 1.5 years depending upon the usage. It cannot be reused","votes":"0","username":"Sandessh Mohite","date":"2022-03-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is Difference beetween kent elegant and kent elegant lite ?","answer":"Pls search on google difference between kent elegant and kent elegant lite model","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Sharma","date":"2022-03-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62ab45bd1cfba6a78772dbb5"},"product_asin":"B08JQQQT17","QAs":[{"question":"can it remove apple coating","answer":"No, not at all. Its a most useless product by Kent.","votes":"0","username":"Sharmas","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it remove wax from apple?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sharmas","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62ab45e31cfba6a78772dc44"},"product_asin":"B08QWYJVS4","QAs":[{"question":"Please suggest best kent model for a 3 members family. Our tds is 260","answer":"Dont buy any purifier with RO in it as it will destroy your TDS level. Anyways dont buy kent the after sales service is terrible.","votes":"0","username":"Rosemary Gomes","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require voltage stabiliser","answer":"Not required","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62ab45fd1cfba6a78772dce3"},"product_asin":"B08QWZJT9G","QAs":[{"question":"Please suggest best kent model for a 3 members family. Our tds is 260","answer":"Dont buy any purifier with RO in it as it will destroy your TDS level. Anyways dont buy kent the after sales service is terrible.","votes":"0","username":"Rosemary Gomes","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require voltage stabiliser","answer":"Not required","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has filter change indicator?","answer":"No, for this model","votes":"0","username":"R@j4u","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62ab46221cfba6a78772dda3"},"product_asin":"B096XHHTVC","QAs":[{"question":"Will you advise on TDS prior to buying?","answer":"Yes it is required . I suggest you to not to go with this because it can only purify water upto 200 tds only. You should go with purifier having 2000 tds","votes":"0","username":"Yamini singh","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have storage","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mohit","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62ae9a291cfba6a787747cde"},"product_asin":"B09KBVNTQD","QAs":[{"question":"Do we have cold water option?","answer":"No, same condition as per inlet water","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Free installation available?","answer":"Free installation available","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the amc cost?","answer":"1000","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hot water option?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can be used for which TDS level?","answer":"Tds > 300","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the more noisy in the product?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation will be done by whom","answer":"Blue star engineer","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outside body material  ?","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we have cold water option?","answer":"No, same condition as per inlet water","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Free installation available?","answer":"Free installation available","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the amc cost?","answer":"1000","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hot water option?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can be used for which TDS level?","answer":"Tds > 300","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the more noisy in the product?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation will be done by whom","answer":"Blue star engineer","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outside body material  ?","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Deokate","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"}]}
